HEROIN Alexis

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

CONTACT

(437) 849-1638

alexis.heroin@outlook.com

Toronto, ON, Canada

in alexis-heroin

alexis-heroin.ca

SKILLS

PROFESSIONAL

- PHP (Laravel, Symfony)
- React / Angular
- Python
- JAVA
- Drupal
- SOL
- Gitlab CI/CD
- Docker

Languages

- French
- English

EDUCATION

MASTER'S DEGREE

Professional Title "IT Expert" EPSI 2017 - 2022

2-year French national post-secondary diploma BTS SIO

BTS SIO EPSI 2017 - 2019

PROFILE

I am a software developer with 4 years of experience in this field. Throughout the various projects I have worked on, I have learned how to work as part of a team, collaborate, and communicate effectively. In fact, in the past few months, I even took on the role of Tech Lead, where I learned how to manage a team, support them, and drive them forward.

I am highly motivated to learn new things and share the skills I have acquired. I believe that I can be a valuable asset in pushing a team forward and, of course, delivering quality output within deadlines. I am available right now and I am extremely motivated. It would be a pleasure to discuss further!

WORK EXPERIENCE

ANGULAR DEVELOPER

onepoint | July 2022 - May 2023

Developed a web site in Angular for the brand 'Provoly' which is a smart cities project. The team is made up of around twenty people.

- Develop the Front End interface using Angular, NgRx and RxJS
- Uses and updated custom library to create multiple application with the same functionality
- Supervise and help juniors

ANGULAR AND PYTHON DEVELOPER

onepoint | Sep 2021 - June 2022

Developed an admin application for intern uses in a 3 developer team.

- Develop API using python and MySQL
- Create client interface using Angular
- Refactor backend organization

LARAVEL API DEVELOPER

onepoint | Sep 2019 - Sep 2021

Developed the game engine and CI/CD pipeline for the serious game project 'Gamabu' in a 10 developer team for thousands of players:

- Build API game engine using Laravel.
- Deploy application using Docker and Gitlab CI/CD
- AWS Lambda and S3

FULLSTACK JAVASCRIPT DEVELOPER

onepoint | Jan 2019 - Mar 2019

Developed an HR application to help the assignment to missions based on skills and travel time:

- Build API game engine using Node.js and Express.js
- Create the interface using React, HTML5 and CSS3

REFERENCES

Portfolio: https://alexis-heroin.ca
Github: https://qithub.com/Malzik
Gamabu: https://www.gamabu.com
Provoly: https://www.provoly.com

React native game; https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.thetraquenard.corpo